Hmm!
- You liked it?
- Hmm!
Very tasty! Thank you!
Thank you so much.
I also love what you've
done with the place.
- It's all you.
- Of course.
What's your reaction
to moving house?
It's fine. It’s just that
the house is a bit small.
"A bit small?"
I'll have a palace built for you.
Zee, could you give me some money
to build a palace for my son?
- Just a minute.
- Come on.
Whose house is this, son?
Dad, it's our house.
Did NBIDC give us a new house?
Dad, we're in Bombay.
We were in Navi Mumbai, weren't we?
Now we're in Bombay, Dad.
Do you work at NBIDC as well?
Dad, he's Xerxes,
my senior, and we work at Tata.
- Namaste, Uncle.
- Namaste.
Dad, please sit
and have lunch with us.
No, Kumud.
Please bring my food to my room.
- Okay?
- Okay.
Bye, Mr. 'Jersey'.
Bye, Uncle.
Bye.
Excuse me.
Do you want something?
No, thank you.
We're planning our future,
but my dad is forgetting the past.
He's gradually forgetting
everything.
'Mr. Desai and Akash's company'
'was still in the project phase.'
'The Watch Project.'
'There was still time for the
project to develop into a company.'
'Step 1-Research.'
'What kind of research?'
'Market research, product analysis,
and customer base.'
'They had to visit different places
to do the ground research.'
'Only then could they move
to the next step.'
'And it was Step 2-Employees.'
'Sikha Agarwal.'
'Nikhil Sharma.'
'Tanya Singh.'
Tanya, sell us this paper.
Sir, I'm here to sell watches,
not paper.
I can give a 90% discount
on this paper.
Are you planning to make
the company incur a loss?
No! No! No!
Your company might incur a loss
if you don't hire me.
Such overconfidence is not good.
Sir, I'm confident
in demonstrating the product
qualities to the customers.
"Our product is really nice."
Saying that is not enough
for the customers.
What about relatability?
That's the point!
A discount
convinces people immediately.
And that's relatability.
At least try it once.
Please sell us this paper.
If I tell you my secret,
it will be a loss for me, so...
Huh?
If the task is to sell
this piece of paper,
then...
Sir, the Four Ps.
CRM and KPIs
can help us win the world.
What does CRM stand for?
CRM, sir...
Try hiring someone else in my place.
Then you'll regret not hiring me.
Okay, we'll hire someone else.
Thank you!
Excuse me?
A 50% discount.
'C', 'R', 'M'...
"CRM."
- A 30% discount.
- Huh?
- Consumer...
- "Consumer."
A 10% discount?
Sir, CRM stands for...
I can't remember.
- Should I leave?
- Oh, yes!
What are you trying to say?
Multipurpose, sir.
People... Especially Indians.
If we show them
the multiple benefits of a product,
in addition to its primary use,
they are more likely to buy it.
What multiple advantages of a watch
can you show the customers?
Sir, in practical terms,
a watch only tells the time.
But if I give this watch
to my daughter,
it will become
a cherished memory for her.
And when she gives it to her
daughter, it will become a legacy.
And if I give it
to my company's employee,
this watch will become
their goodwill or pride.
Sir, the customers
will come to buy a watch,
but will leave with a feeling
of a deep connection.
Hmm.
So, Miss Megha Mhatre,
we'll be in touch.
Thank you.
Thank you, sir.
- It's already five.
- Hmm.
Sir, these are the resumes.
Candidates are waiting outside.
Oi, Zee.
How will we interview
so many engineers?
- It's already five o'clock.
- Hmm.
They are twelve.
Let's have a demonstration
instead of a discussion.
If the fan works,
the job is yours.
Sir,
will an electrician's task
judge the capability of engineers?
If you don't want the job,
you may leave.
Anyone?
Good.
Kindly take your positions.
Your time starts now!
- Whoa!
- Please be careful, my friend!
Be careful, guys!
Whoa!
Relax.
Okay, guys.
Ten...
Nine...
Eight...
Seven...
Six...
Five...
Four!
Three...
Two...
One! Time's up!
You just made it.
Sir, please turn on the fans.
Whoa!
God!
Oh, wow!
Thank you, everyone.
All the best for the future.
- Let's go.
- And, sir,
your name is Mr...
Gaurav.
- "Gaurav."
Gaurav Dhar?
So, Mr. Gaurav Dhar,
had you been informed
about today's test?
- No, sir.
- No?
No, sir.
Sir, I love machines,
not my position.
Be it a printing press, fans,
or complex machines like watches.
- Good job.
- Well done.
- Thank you.
- Look at this.
Sir, am I...
Sir?
10 a.m. tomorrow.
- Thank you. Sir, my hands...
- Uh-uh!
- Okay.
- That's okay.
- Welcome to the Watch Project.
- Thank you, sir.
Whoa!
We'll have to call a mechanic
along with an electrician.
I'm used to it.
Anyway, congratulations.
See you tomorrow.
[in Marathi] Hello, Megha.
[in Marathi] Your mother
is truly proud of you.
[in Marathi] But why?
[in Marathi] This is the first time
someone has reached
such great heights
in our neighbourhood.
And Tata, no less!
[in Marathi] Mom, is it true?
Yes!
Aunt Sheela got a call.
You have to join
at 10 a.m. tomorrow.
You won't have to run the packed
lunch service from tomorrow.
You must rest now.
- It doesn't work that way.
- Why not?
- What should I do?
- No, leave it.
I can do this.
Malti's Subbu is waiting outside.
Please go and meet him.
You might even get
a marriage proposal.
I don't want to marry, Mom.
How many times should I tell you?
At least meet him once.
Please go. Please do as I say.
Go and see him.
Ms. Megha.
Shall we go out for an ice cream?
Yes?
My name is Ravindra Naik,
and I suffer from flatulence.
I mean, I'm a professor
at the J.J. School of Arts.
Could you please call ma'am?
Sorry, Mom can't make
any more packed lunches.
But she agreed this morning.
Mom, if you keep serving others,
when will you eat?
I'm helpless.
Otherwise, I would have eaten out.
Okay.
She'll cook for you every day,
but she'll charge
four rupees per lunchbox.
Are you doubling the rates?
Since we're stretching our limits,
you should stretch yours too.
Megha, he has a problem.
So? What about your problems?
We run a packed lunch service,
not a hospital, Mom.
Tell me, sir.
Four rupees per lunchbox. Okay?
Health is more important.
Okay, I'll pay four rupees.
Welcome to Sudha's Lunchbox Service.
- Thank you.
- Welcome.
Tell me, where do you want
to go for an ice cream?
No! No!
We can go later.
The ice cream vendor
would still be there.
Bye!
Megha! Megha! Megha!
Today is your first day at work,
so this is for you.
I'm running late.
'Akash.'
Kumud, I'm running late.
- 'Akash!'
- Yes?
At least have some
sweetened curd before you go.
Oh!
- All the best.
- Thank you!
Bye!
Hello, I'm Megha Mhatre.
Hi! I'm Gaurav.
Um... I was talking to him.
Oh! Sorry!
Mr. Gaurav Dhar?
This is your ID card.
Yes, thank you.
You are...
- Marketing.
- Okay.
- And you?
- I'm the head engineer.
Which college?
IIT.
Megha Mhatre, please take your card.
Are you from IIM?
No, I'm from Lady Shri Ram College.
- Shall we?
- Yes, let's go. Please.
- Excuse me, sir.
- Yes?
- Your bag.
- Oh!
He's joking.
Oh.
Megha, please help Akash
make the proposal.
- Gaurav, please come here.
- Yes, sir.
Sir, this was prepared by my mother.
We cannot pitch today,
come what may.
I can't say no
to the Tata Board, Akash.
Hmm! This is amazing.
- Zee.
- Yes?
Our meeting
was scheduled for next month.
We are not prepared yet.
Yes, but it was brought forward,
so we have to prepare.
That's that.
Megha, come here.
- Watch... A mechanical watch
has six main components. - Okay.
- There's a barrel spring.
- Correct.
It has a hand-setting mechanism.
- And...
- Train wheels and cases.
Oh! Very good!
You're one step ahead.
Memorise all the other components.
You'll need it for the pitch.
What pitch, sir?
The Watch Project pitch.
Sir, is the Watch Project
not confirmed yet?
Welcome
to the world of Xerxes Desai.
We’re caught between a rock
and a hard place.
Oi, you!
Don't stress them out.
- Okay.
- This is a manual on quartz.
- "Quartz?"
- This... Yes.
Go through it thoroughly.
Be prepared
for any kind of question.
These are the bullet points
for the feasibility report.
You have two hours.
Just fine-tune the entire proposal.
Also, remember everything. Okay?
Take this.
Only two hours, sir?
Yes, is it a lot?
It took us a year and a half
to collect this data.
You just have to
write it beautifully.
- You can do it.
- Okay?
- Zee.
- Hmm?
Please do as I say.
We don't even have any experts.
We'll get them.
- Loan?
- We'll get it.
If we pitch unprepared,
the entire Watch Project
might be cancelled.
Can we request them
to delay this meeting?
Please.
Thanks.
Hello, Operator.
Please connect me to Bombay House,
Bombay.
Yes, I'd like to speak to Mr. Tata.
Yes, J.R.D.
J.R.D.
Tell him.
Tell him that we can't make it.
- See you in five minutes.
- Yes.
Don't be nervous.
Go inside
and convince them.
Why don't you come with us?
- No, I can't.
- Why not?
The Board will accept
the Watch Project immediately.
Everyone will listen to you.
Zee, you have to convince them
through your potential,
not through my status.
Jeh, who took on the challenge
of making watches?
"Symbol of excellence."
Don't try
any of your 'Desaisms' on me.
You must fight your own battle.
Okay, tell me.
What's the probability
of a yes or a no?
- Fifty-fifty.
- Fifty-fifty means yes.
You passed.
What's the logic?
The logic is that producing watches
is our dream.
A dream without passion
and conviction is doomed to fail.
If you can't convince them,
how do you expect me
to entrust you with this company?
Hmm?
Come on.
Collect all the watches
in the office
and bring them to me.
Why?
No discussion,
only demonstration.
"All the watches."
Zee.
Hello! Good afternoon.
Good afternoon, everyone.
May I? Very nice!
May I borrow your watch?
Everyone's watch, please.
Just give it to Gaurav
and Megha, please.
Please humour me. Don't worry.
I'll give them back.
This box contains all the watches
from the entire building.
My colleague
has also collected the clocks,
which I didn't ask for.
But...
It's fine.
Pulsar.
Seiko.
Citizen.
Pulsar...
What's the catch, Mr. Desai?
The catch is that
none of the watches
are made in India.
Pick up the one in the corner.
I wear a GMT watch.
It's made in India.
Fine.
One watch is made in India.
One watch out of...
You cannot judge
the requirement of the whole country
based on the requirement
of this room.
We aren't.
Sir, GMT manufactures
one million watches a year in India.
Allwyn and other small companies
manufacture around 800,000 watches.
The total number of watches
manufactured in India
every year is 1.8 million.
We know that.
Yes, sir.
But, sir, do you know
how many watches
are sold in India every year?
More than five million.
The difference between
these two figures is 3.2 million.
And the smugglers
are taking advantage of this gap.
Yes.
Yes, and these smuggled watches
are in demand
because they upgrade with time.
Which is exactly what we want to do.
We want to dominate this market.
Suppose watches are in demand,
but you are looking at it
only in terms of sales.
What about the first step,
manufacturing?
Sir, if GMT can, so can we.
GMT has the best collaborators
in the world.
It has Citizen.
Allwyn has Seiko.
Who do you have, Desai?
We can find
collaborators and experts, sir.
It's a serious investment, Desai.
I know.
Which one do you have at the moment?
At the moment, we...
Sir!
We trust Xerxes.
The world doesn't run
on trust, Mr...
Akash.
Yes, Akash.
The world runs on practicality.
Sir, if we don't...
Yes, sir.
Let's take a break. Hmm?
Thank you, sir.
Excuse me, sirs.
Have you seen the inside of a watch?
Gaurav...
This is a mechanical watch.
Beautiful, right?
But we won't make this.
We will manufacture this one.
I love mechanical watches,
but I'll 'marry' quartz.
See. Here...
That's the quartz crystal.
You want to produce watches
and even experiment
with new technology?
Yes, sir.
- Because quartz is the future.
- Yes!
It really is.
GMT primarily manufactures
mechanical watches.
They hardly produce quartz watches.
I'm sure they have a good reason.
Maybe.
Or maybe they aren't even thinking.
That's because
they don't have any competition.
But our designs and technology
will revolutionise the way
Indians think about luxury.
They sell watches,
but we'll sell dreams
to every Indian.
Sir, your watch is dead.
Sir, mechanical watches
are beautiful,
but they need to be
wound repeatedly.
Your time is precious, Mr. Singh.
You can't afford to lose
track of time like this.
That's why we have to move on.
We have to move on
to this self-sustaining technology.
Gaurav...
Sir, we need 120 to 180 components
to produce a mechanical watch.
On the other hand, a quartz watch
requires only 60 to 70 components.
It's a simple technology.
This is why its manufacturing cost
and time will be much lower, sir.
We don't have to do much.
Look at the battery.
Quartz watches run on batteries.
Just take the battery
and...
That's it, sir.
It will function smoothly
for two to three years.
Well done.
Desai, if you truly want to start
a new venture, choose a safe one.
Go for large-scale manufacturing,
like Tata Steel and Tata Motors.
Go big!
We are Tatas.
Exactly, sir. Exactly!
If we don't create history,
who will?
Creating history is one thing,
and becoming history is another.
I hope you understand
what we are afraid of, Mr. Desai.
Since when did we
start being afraid?
Mr. Jamsetji Tata was the founder
of India's first steel plant,
which was subsequently started
by Mr. Dorabji Tata.
The British made fun of him
and ridiculed his abilities.
Yet he sold them steel during the
First World War, making a profit.
When Jamsetji was denied
entry to the Watson Hotel,
where the noticeboard read,
"Dogs and Indians are not allowed",
he went on to create Asia's biggest
luxury five-star hotel chain.
The Taj Mahal Palace,
equipped
with the first electric lift.
Sir, we knew nothing
about consumerism,
yet we launched
Tata Tea and Tata Salt.
Today, the whole nation
wakes up with our tea.
What about the IT industry, Akash?
Yes, sir.
We had no knowledge
of information technology.
Yet TCS has been making
a profit for the past 12 years.
Sir, we've travelled
through the sky.
Can't we manufacture a watch?
Thank you, Akash.
Sometimes, it takes a new face
to remind us of our history.
Besides, Mr. Singh,
we are sticking with the engine.
This watch is the smallest engine
in the world.
It is a marvel.
No offence, gentlemen,
but if I were in your place,
I would put my career,
my life, my everything
at stake for this project.
We should have a quick vote.
Those in favour
of the Watch Project,
raise your hands.
Those who are not in favour,
please raise your hands.
You've got a tie.
But
looking at your passion for quartz,
I cast you my vote, Desai.
I've seen your report,
and it's clear that you need
substantial funding.
KBI will definitely give you a loan.
Please send your licence proposal
to the government for approval.
All the best.
Thank you, sir.
Thank you.
So?
What's the decision?
51%.
Sir, the Watch Project
is good to go.
Congratulations!
Sorry, I was a little late.
But you can't be late.
- Zee.
- Hmm?
I drafted the licence application.
Please review before applying.
Please do come and feel at home.
Do you eat here nowadays?
The food goes cold
by the time it reaches home.
Your mom suggested I eat here.
Why did you make 'laddus'?
You've received a marriage proposal
from an IPS officer.
Whether or not our watches
get manufactured,
you want me to marry. Am I right?
'How will you live alone
after I'm gone, Megha?'
Many people live alone in Bombay.
I can too.
I won't marry
just for the sake of company.
What if I lose my job
because of my marriage?
You'd be burdened once again.
"Burden?"
Don't say that, my dear.
Why don't you understand, Mom?
A woman has no identity
without marriage, my child.
How could you say that, Mom?
Has our proposal been rejected?
We'll find a way.
Zee, I don't want to lose this job.
- Ever since I left NBIDC...
- Yes! Yes.
You've mentioned it.
I was talking to Kumud
and Dad last night,
- and I was...
- I have a family too, Akash.
But Tata will assign you
to another project.
- What about me?
- Let me think.
Why are you avoiding me?
Your friend
is asking you a question.
"Friend?"
What responsibility
did you fulfil as a friend?
It was your job to read the
government regulations, wasn't it?
How could you miss the MRTP Act?
Didn't I fulfil my responsibility?
Yes.
What about your responsibilities?
Loans and experts were supposed
to be brought by you.
Where are they?
We were not rejected
for either loans or experts.
We were rejected
because of the MRTP Act.
Come on!
Don't pretend it was all my fault.
It is!
The Watch Project was your idea,
and there has been a mistake in it.
If the core is wrong,
there's no point in covering it up.
I stood by you,
believing in your idea.
But what did you do?
You keep talking
about family and job,
yet you couldn't even do
your one job!
I don't even know
what your contribution
to the Watch Project is!
I'm sorry, I...
I didn't mean that...
This sorry...
Is it from a friend or a boss?
What boss? I'm your friend.
I forgive my friend.
But, Zee,
I quit.
I can't work under such uncertainty
with a boss like that.
I'm sorry, Zee.
I quit.
It's just a single rejection.
"A single rejection?"
The project is dead
before it even started.
they needed lifts.
But the lifts were too slow.
The person waiting
for the lift would get bored,
and the one inside
would feel claustrophobic.
- Hmm. - The plan to build
skyscrapers was in jeopardy.
Who would buy a flat
on the 50th or 60th floor
of a building without a lift?
- Right?
- Right.
So,
do you know what they did?
Did they build high-speed lifts?
That technology
was still years away.
They installed mirrors in the lifts.
- Mirrors.
- All right.
So that one could see one's face,
adjust one's clothes,
set one's hair,
and reach one's floor
before even realising it.
Right.
Such a simple solution
to a serious problem.
Right?
I'm sure you'll find
your own 'mirror' too.
But today,
your only challenge
is to beat me.
Come on!
Dad.
- Dad!
- Hmm?
The tea has turned cold.
And please eat something.
Okay?
Are you happy working at NBIDC?
I work for Tata, Dad.
I mean, I used to.
Please eat something.
Are you happy where you are?
- No.
- Why?
Because of Xerxes.
The man who came
for lunch the other day.
Do you remember my senior at NBIDC?
I used to say he had
a solution to every problem.
I thought he could cure
even my boredom.
That's why I followed him
and joined Tata.
But after coming here,
I realised he was crazy.
Although he had left NBIDC,
he didn't sit still.
He had a simple desk job,
but he wanted a challenge.
If he really wanted
to start a new venture,
he could have chosen a safe one.
But no.
What did he choose?
Watch manufacturing.
There was so much pressure
that I couldn't handle it.
Strangely, despite the chaos
of working with him,
I enjoyed it a lot.
They suddenly gave me
a kind of relief,
after a life
that had been so boring.
Have you gone mad like him?
Yes, Dad.
That company
is full of insane people.
Perhaps I've become one of them.
I work for the passion,
not the money.
I guess, yes. I...
I've gone crazy.
And maybe I can't live
without the craziness.
Thanks, Dad.
Water!
Do you need more?
I've found the solution.
What is it?
The MRTP Act.
That's the problem, Akash.
It's the solution too. Listen.
According to the MRTP Act,
large-scale companies aren't allowed
to manufacture watches, right?
- Right. - But there's no mention
of whether a sister company
or a company funded by a large
corporation can enter the market.
What if we don't enter
the market as the Tatas,
but as an investment company
under Tata?
Hello, Operator?
Please connect me to Madras.
The number is 6246004.
- Do you need more?
- One more glass, please.
Shankar?
Come on, it's really good.
You want to convince
TIDCO's chairman
with a 'laddu'?
No, it's not like that.
Is it working, though?
- It's good.
- Hmm.
Why not Maharashtra
or any other state?
Any state can give you land.
You gave me the idea of watches,
so why should we give the profit
from a land deal to someone else?
I would've signed the deal
immediately if it were in my hands,
but the minister won't agree.
Why, sir?
He doesn't trust capitalists.
I can arrange a meeting with him.
But he won't agree.
"TIDCO!"
It's good.
I could really use
your help here, Jeh.
The minister
apparently hates capitalists.
- Whoa! Really?
- Yes.
We have a meeting with him
the day after tomorrow at 2 p.m.
Well, book us on the 9 a.m. flight.
Great!
Hello!
Rishabh, you need
to understand one thing.
When you're dealing with me,
please be clear
with the numbers,
because I am. Locked.
Thank you, Rishabh.
- Sir, you called us urgently.
- Hmm.
All okay, sir?
No, you're fired.
Sir, you are just...
Yes.
Your termination letters.
Sorry, guys.
- Sir, but what happened?
- Sir...
Stop it!
Sir, sorry?
You're fired,
because you're hired
in our new company.
- Okay.
- Sir...
Who are Questar Investments?
Well, we're now
a small independent investment firm.
Yes!
How is a small investment firm
supposed to compete with GMT?
We're a small independent
investment firm
backed by the Tatas.
Just because our firm is small,
that doesn't diminish
our thinking or our dreams.
Right?
Right, sir.
What's the time?
- Sir, 8:30.
- It's 8:30, sir.
- It's 8:30.
- Fine.
You two don't wear watches?
Because we haven't made one yet.
Welcome to Questar Investments.
Thank you, sir.
- Thank you, sir.
- It's a pleasure.
Nervous?
I just really want this to go well.
You know, Zee,
you have a basic problem.
Which one?
Whatever comes to your mind
shows clearly on your face.
Oh!
You should keep this in mind.
When you meet a client,
you should keep a straight face.
- "A straight face?"
- Yes.
I've started referring to
a Hindi dictionary, inspired by you.
A straight face
means an expressionless face.
- Oh!
- No expression.
- Hmm?
- Hmm.
The client should know nothing
about what's in your head.
If you laugh first,
he'll take you for granted.
If he sees that you're nervous,
he'll underestimate you.
Always remember this.
Your face shouldn't show
a single wrinkle.
But your face has so many wrinkles.
Ah! Touché.
- Shankar.
- Sir?
[in Tamil] Are you serious?
[in Tamil]
I won't give away our lands
for their profit.
[in Tamil] Sir, please wait
at least until the meeting.
They are the ones
making us wait right now.
The appointment is at 2 p.m., sir.
Good afternoon, gentlemen.
I trust we're on time.
Right, Xerxes?
Yes, sir.
Did you also stop wearing a watch?
Sir, please.
Thank you!
I apologise,
but we're a little short of time.
So, if you don't mind, we should
discuss the terms and conditions
of the agreement now.
What terms and conditions?
We didn't agree
to give away our land.
Not your terms and conditions,
I'm talking about ours.
In exchange for the land,
I'm offering you a collaboration
between TIDCO and the Tatas.
"TIDCO and the Tatas?"
And in that collaboration,
27.88% of the stakes
will belong to TIDCO.
Stakes, Jeh?
Sir.
That's almost 28%.
Are you serious or joking?
I never joke when I
talk about business.
We're not here
just for the land or the factories.
I want to start an industry.
It will benefit the people
of Tamil Nadu, not just us,
because we will employ only locals.
So, employment,
stakes, collaboration,
and the Tatas.
What more incentive do you need?
[in Tamil] Sir,
other state governments
would jump at the chance.
Akash, give him the MOU.
What's wrong with your face?
A straight face!
[in Gujarati]
Do you need anything else?
[in Gujarati] And where
did you learn Gujarati?
[in Gujarati] Tell me quickly.
Do you need anything?
A minimum of one year's training
with French collaborators.
You took the words
right out of my mouth.
And they must undertake
one year of training
with French experts.
- Fine.
- Sir.
No, not me. Xerxes is the founder.
Sign it.
Who will be your GM?
Shyama Krishna Gopalan.
- When is he expected?
- Any minute now.
He seems to be
a serious person.
Focus on his work,
not his appearance.
His strategies
worked wonders
at Belfast Electronics.
- No, really.
- Look.
Look at his face.
It seems he'll come over and say,
"Hi, this is Shyama Krishna Gopalan.
S.K. Gopalan. Are you Xerox Desai?"
Hello!
You are
Mr. 'Xerzex' Desai?
Actually, I'm Xerxes,
but you can call me Zee or Desai.
I would prefer "Mr. Desai".
Please!
Thank you.
I happen to be
S.K. Gopalan.
Yes.
Welcome to the Watch Project.
Oh, thank you. Thank you so much.
Um...
Is there no formal name
for the company yet?
Gaurav.
Idea?
I think it should be
something mythological.
- Megha? - Can we think
of something different, sir?
- Like Nike, the Greek Goddess.
- No!
There are thousands of brands
with mythological names.
Think of something else.
Volkswagen means
"people's car" in German.
If we want to say, "people's watch",
it could be 'Lokghadi'.
It's an atrocious idea.
- No! No!
- Sorry! Chuck it.
Think of an easy name
that reflects our brand value.
Uh, Gopalan.
- It's a government letter.
- Thank you.
We finally got the licence.
Is it done?
Phew!
- So taking it from there...
- Hmm.
I was thinking, Nescafé got its name
- from its parent company,
Nestlé, right? - Hmm.
And what is our parent company?
- Tata Industries?
- Hmm.
And our partner is...
TIDCO.
So what if we derive
something from these two...
- Don't you think
this name is too long? - Entities.
Not ours.
- Tata Industries Tamil Nadu.
- We can work on it.
No.
We need a name
that represents
our strength, legacy,
and ambition.
- Right?
- Yes, sir.
I agree.
Titan.
Mr. Desai...
Hmm?
That's so nice.
- Man!
- Well done!
- Congratulations!
- Sir, it's perfect.
Oh, good! Nice?
- It's nice.
- Is it?
- Yes.
- Right?
It's good.
'Titan?'
- Yes.
- Hmm.
I've never heard it before.
The company is registered,
but it hasn't been established yet.
Then why do you need a loan?
To establish the company.
You see, we've had a long-standing
relationship with the Tatas.
- Hmm.
- Yes.
But producing watches
is a risky business.
Well...
On top of that, you want to
manufacture quartz watches, right?
Yes.
It contributes only 5%
to GMT's total sales.
- Yes, because they focus on...
- Do you know something?
Why is people's money
safe in our bank?
Not because of tight security,
but because we never
put their money at risk.
Yes... No.
- Sir, I know it's a bit...
- I'm sorry, Mr. Desai.
If any other bank
is willing to take the risk,
all the best,
but we cannot grant you a loan.
I'm sorry.
'Sorry, Mr. Desai. We cannot
grant your company a loan.'
'Your loan application
has been rejected.'
'No one will understand
this technology.'
'Quartz? What is that?'
'We are not ready to invest in you.
Sorry!'
'I'm sorry,
your loan has been rejected.'
'This technology is rather new.'
'Sorry, Mr. Desai.
We can't grant you a loan.'
'- People won't understand it.
- Your loan has been rejected.'
'- Sorry, Mr. Desai.
- Sorry!'
---